ringpartner.com 2019-12-27

# Privacy Policy — RingPartner

Thank you for visiting the RingPartner Network (“Network”) at www.ringpartner.com (the "Site"). RingPartner ("we", "us") is committed to protecting the privacy of your personally identifiable information. We provide this privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") in order to explain how and what information is collected or used to create and maintain the Site, and what choices you have in respect to your information.  
You must agree to this Privacy Policy, in its entirety, in order to register an account ("Account") by completing a Client or Publisher Application, and to be able to log into your Account as member of the Network. Your acceptance of both this Privacy Policy and our use of cookies on the Site shall be deemed a blanket acceptance of such Privacy Policy and cookie usage for all future attempts to log-in and access your Account. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy in its entirety, you are not authorized to register for an Account on the Network.

## Commitment to Privacy:

Protecting your information is of the utmost importance to us, as is maintaining compliance with any governing authority to which the processing of personal information may occur for any of our services. The European Union ("EU") maintains strict privacy laws through General Data Privacy Regulation ("GDPR"). This standard differs significantly from Canadian or U.S. law. We comply with regulations where it applies to the processing of personal data, the disclosure of the appropriate notifications, and, where applicable, with provision of a process by which you can request the erasure of your personal information.

## What Information Do We Collect? 

We collect personally identifiable information when you complete a Client or Publisher Application, or otherwise choose to provide personally identifiable information to us. We may also collect personally identifiable information when phone call(s) made by you or any consumer that are routed through RingPartner to a Client of RingPartner’s are recorded. Personally identifiable information is any information that can be used to identify or locate a particular person or entity.

This may include but is not limited to: your name, business entity name and/or your title with the applicable business entity, as well as your personal and/or business entity related e-mail address, mailing address, daytime and/or cellular telephone numbers, account information (or other information that we require in order to pay any amounts due to you, or collect amounts payable by you, under the Network), any information that is disclosed during a phone call that is recorded, and/or any other information requested on the applicable registration form. For purposes of this Privacy Policy, your account information shall be considered "Sensitive Information."

## Use of Your Information:

How we use the information we collect depends in part on the manner in which such personally identifiable information is disclosed to us, which services of the Network you use, how you use them, and/or any preferences you have communicated to us. Below are specific purposes for which we use the information we collect:

  * ### To provide the Network services and personalize your experience.

We use information about you to provide the Network services to you, including to authenticate you when you log in, process payments to or from you, provide customer support, and operate and maintain the Network. For example, we use the name and account details you provide us to identify you to your Account.

  * ### To communicate with you about your Account.

We may send you information regarding your Account and the Network, including the status of your Account or billing.

  * ### To promote new Campaigns.

If you have a Publisher Account, we use your contact information and information about how you use the Network to send communications via e-mail about Campaigns that may be of specific interest to you. For Client or Publisher Accounts, we may also send e-mail communications with information about new features, survey requests, newsletter, or events we think may be of interest to you.  
You agree that we may contact you at any time with updates and/or any other information that we may deem appropriate for you to receive in connection with your Account on the Network. If you wish to opt out of e-mail newsletters, you may do so by clicking on the unsubscribe links located at the bottom of such emails. In addition, you may request to have your personal information removed from our Network by e-mailing [privacy@ringpartner.com](chrome-extension://bpmcpldpdmajfigpchkicefoigmkfalc/views/qowt.html#mailto:privacy@ringpartner.com).

  * ### Customer Support.

We use your information to respond to your requests for assistance and general correspondence, and to resolve technical issues, if any, you may encounter.

  * ### For quality assurance purposes.

Phone calls that we route to a Client of ours may be recorded for quality assurance purposes only. We take steps to protect such information from inadvertent disclosure, do not sell such information to third parties, and only retain such information for so long as is necessary to validate the phone calls.

  * ### For safety and security.

We use information about you and your use of the Network to verify accounts and activity, to monitor suspicious or fraudulent activity, and to identify violations of Network policies and Terms and Conditions.

  * ### To protect our legitimate business interests and legal rights.

Where required by law or where we believe it is necessary to protect our legal rights, interests and the interests of others, we use information about you in connection with legal claims, compliance, regulatory, and audit functions, and disclosures in connection with the acquisition, merger or sale of a business.

  * ### With your consent. 

We use information about you where you have given us consent to do so for a specific purpose not listed above. For example, we may publish testimonials or featured customer or client stories to promote the Network, with your permission.

  * ### Legal basis for processing (for EEA users). 

If you are an individual in the European Economic Area (EEA), we collect and process information about you only where we have legal basis for doing so under applicable EU laws. The legal basis depends on the Network services you use and how you use them. This means we collect and use your information only where:

  * We need it to provide you the Network services, including to operate the Network, provide customer support and personalized features, and to protect the safety and security of the Network;

  * It satisfies a legitimate interest (which is not overridden by your data protection interests), such as for research and development, to market and promote the Network and to protect our legal rights and interests;

  * You give us consent to do so for a specific purpose; or

  * We need to process your data to comply with a legal obligation.

If you have consented to our use of information about you for a specific purpose, you have the right to change your mind at any time, but this will not affect any processing that has already taken place. Where we are using your information because we or a third have a legitimate interest to do so, you have the right to object to that use though, in some cases, this may mean no longer using the Network.

## Portal Used in Connection with Your Account. 

When you register for an Account on the Network, we use a password-protected third party portal to store your personal information, and we may share your personal information with such third party ("Third Party Agent") as is necessary for the performance of your Account and the Network.

## Information Sharing. 

As a general rule, and other than in connection with the limited exceptions set forth below, we will not sell, share or rent your personally identifiable information to or with others, except in limited circumstance where we have your express consent. Notwithstanding the foregoing, we may, from time to time, provide such information to certain third-party administrative vendors for efficiency purposes in providing administrative or program management services, or to serve emails on our behalf, in connection with your Account. Any third-party vendor so used has agreed to protect the confidentiality of information provided by us.   
Further, we reserve the right to share your personally identifiable information: (a) where required by law, or requested by a court of competent jurisdiction; (b) in the event of any reorganization, merger, sale, joint venture, assignment, transfer or other disposition of all or any portion of our business, assets or stock; (c) where you are in violation of this Privacy Policy, and/or the Terms and Conditions; (d) in the case of a dispute; or (e) where we determine, in our sole discretion, that such disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or a third party, or necessary to protect us from liability of any kind. The aforementioned includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection.

## Non-Personally Identifiable Information. 

We may collect certain non-personally identifiable information about you when you visit certain pages of this Site and/or register for an Account on the Network, such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Chrome, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Windows 10 or Mac OS) and the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., America Online, Earthlink), and share such information with our Third Party Agent. We use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of the Site and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze Site usage.

## Cookies and Web Beacons. 

To enhance your experience with the Site, we use "cookies." You cannot log into the Network without agreeing to accept the cookies that we use with the Site.  
Cookies are small packets of data stored on your computer. Cookies are used by your computer's browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information. We use cookies to understand Site usage and to improve the content and offerings on the Site. You may set your browser to warn you that cookies are in use, or to block the use of cookies. Most browsers are set to accept cookies. If your browser is not set to accept cookies, certain uses of the Site may require you to go to your browser user preferences to enable cookies. Each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences. If you change computers, operating systems or browsers, or use multiple computers or browsers, you will need to repeat this process for each computer and each browser. To find out more about cookies, please visit [www.cookiecentral.com ](http://www.cookiecentral.com./)  
We may additionally collect information using Web beacons, which are commonly referred to in the industry as web bugs, pixel tags or Clear GIFs. Web beacons are electronic images that may be used on the Site, in your Account, or in our emails to deliver cookies, count visits and determine if an email has been opened and acted upon.

## International Transfer of Data. 

If you are located in the European Union or other regions with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from Canadian or U.S. law, please note that you are transferring information and permitting the transfer of information, including personal information, to a country and jurisdiction that does not have the same data protection laws as your jurisdiction. You consent to the transfer of your information to Canada and the United States and the use and disclosure of information about you, including personal information, as described in this Privacy Policy.

## Data Retention. 

Subject to any mandatory obligations to delete data, your information may be retained by us and in our Third Party Agent portal, server logs, databases and records indefinitely.

## Third Party Links. 

The Site may contain links to third-party websites ("Third Party Websites"). Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of Third Party Websites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave the Site and to read the privacy policies of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by the Site.

## Your Employees. 

Your acceptance of the terms of this Privacy Policy, in their entirety, shall extend to your employees, if any. You agree that any of your employees that access your Account or visit the Site under the scope of their employment with you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy.

## Minors. 

We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children and to participate and monitor the interactive activities of their children. We will never knowingly collect any personal information about individuals under eighteen (18) years of age. If we obtain actual knowledge that we have collected personal information about an individual under eighteen (18) years of age, that information will be immediately deleted from its database.

## Security. 

We endeavor to safeguard and protect our Account holders' information. When Account holders submit personally identifiable information to the Network, their personally identifiable information is protected both online and offline. When our registration process asks registrants to submit Sensitive Information, and when we transmit such Sensitive Information, that Sensitive Information is encrypted and protected with SSL encryption software. While we use SSL encryption to protect Sensitive Information online, we protect all other user information online and offline. The Third Party Agent servers that we utilize to store personally identifiable information in are kept in a secure physical environment. The Third Party Agent has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of personally identifiable information stored on its servers.  
Please be advised that, although we take every reasonable precaution available to protect your data, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Therefore, we cannot warrant that your information will be absolutely secure. Any transmission of data at or through our Site is at your own risk. However, access to your personally identifiable information is strictly limited, and not accessible to the public. Only employees, and Third Party Agents, that need the information to perform a specific job are granted access to personally identifiable information. Our employees are dedicated to ensuring the security and privacy of all user information. Employees not adhering to our written firm policies are subject to disciplinary action. In compliance with applicable provincial, federal and state laws, we shall notify you and any applicable regulatory agencies in the event that we learn of an information security breach with respect to your personally identifiable information. You will be notified via e-mail in the event of such a breach. Please be advised that notice may be delayed in order to address the needs of law enforcement, determine the scope of network damage, and to engage in remedial measures.  
You acknowledge that you provide your personally identifiable information to us with knowledgeable consent and at your own risk.

## Deleting and Updating Your Information. 

If you would like to delete or update the personally identifiable information that we have collected from you, simply email us at: privacy@ringpartner.com.   
We will process your request within a reasonable period of time after receipt. To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to help verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

## Opting Out of Receiving E-mail. 

You may at any time choose to stop receiving emails containing general information regarding RingPartner by following the instructions at the end of each such email or by contacting us at privacy@ringpartner.com.  
Should you be contacted by our Third Party Agent through email, you can follow the instructions at the end of each such email to stop receiving such emails. There may be a short delay of up to several business days while your request is being verified, deployed and processed across our servers. Notwithstanding the foregoing, we may continue to contact you for the purpose of communicating information relating to your Account, as well as to respond to any inquiry or request made by you.

## Changes to Privacy Policy. 

We reserve the right to amend or revise this Privacy Policy at any time. We will post any changes to this page. Please check the Site periodically for any changes. Your continued use of the Site and/or acceptance of our e-mail communications following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of any and all changes.

## Can You Access the Personal Information Acquired by Us?

Your personal information can be corrected or updated within your Account in the Network, or by contacting privacy@ringpartner.com.  
For the deletion and erasure of personal information, email privacy@ringpartner.com to begin the process and we will respond to your request within 30 days.

## Contact Us. 

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, or would like more information on our privacy practices, please contact us at: [privacy@ringpartner.com](chrome-extension://bpmcpldpdmajfigpchkicefoigmkfalc/views/qowt.html#mailto:privacy@ringpartner.com) or send correspondence to the following address:

Ring Partner Inc.  
Attn: Data Protection Officer  
200-775 Topaz Avenue, Victoria, BC  
V8T 4Z7
